Ben Garlock

New York, NY | 646-241-6885 | ben.garlock@gmail.com | Github | Blog | LinkedIn | Portfolio

CUSTOMER SUCCESS MANAGER

A Customer Success Manager with a strong emphasis on driving client value using technology and data. Over fifteen years of customer facing experience in troubleshooting complex technical issues with high profile accounts. Patient, organized, and professional.

CORE PROFICIENCIES

Customer Service, De-Escalations, Performance Consultation, Technical Expertise, Product Improvement, Implementation and Training, Product Demonstration, Customer Advocacy, Data Analytics, Customer Engagement.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Sr. Customer Success Manager - OpenTable/Kayak - New York, NY

3/2017 - 5/2020

- Directly responsible for maintaining 300+ elite, high-value OpenTable restaurant partnerships.
- Coordinated with software development teams to provide product feedback, deploy new features, and conduct production tests.
- Utilized data and analytical tools to assist OpenTable partners in optimizing best practices and use of the OpenTable platform including marketing, business development products, and inventory utilization.
- Lead partner's system conversion efforts from a legacy system built on client-server architecture to a cloud-based technology product.

Sr. Customer Operations Consultant - OpenTable - Chicago, IL

4/2007 - 3/2017

- Deployed the OpenTable reservation and guest management system to 2000+ restaurant customers across North America including large-scale hotels, casinos, resorts, and enterprise restaurant groups.
- Provided in-person consultations with restaurant staff to optimize best practices and use of the OpenTable platform.

Sr. Customer Support Technician - OpenTable - San Francisco, CA 3/2004 - 4/2007

- Provided technical and training support to 15,000+ domestic and international OpenTable restaurant customers.
- Managed special project teams to maintain data security, network health, and application patching.
- Resolved high-level service outage issues in high pressure environments.

EDUCATION

Flatiron School

June 2020 - October 2020 Full Stack Web Development. Ruby on Rails, React, JavaScript

DeVry University

June 2001 - March 2004 Computer Network Administration. Bachelor of Science - 127 credits completed